{
    "id": "ee8e74e384e04ae9af627de0d1e9c2c7",
    "title": "Participles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Loudly ……………….. at the door, he demanded admission.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knocking",
                "knocked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... by his friends, he lost all hopes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Deceived",
                "Deceiving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... the loud noise, the boy woke up.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw trees ………………….. with fruits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lading",
                "laden"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... . that all was safe, the old man attempted to cross the road.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Thinking",
                "Thought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "....................... by a dust storm, the troupes fell into disarray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Blinded",
                "Blinding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... by hunger, the boy stole a piece of bread.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Driven",
                "Driving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. for a while, we resumed our journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Resting",
                "Having rested",
                "Rested"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ...................... noise awakened the watchman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "creaking",
                "creaked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Your …………………. coat needs mending.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tattering",
                "tattered"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}